Hello friends welcome to my YouTube channel
friends in this video I am going to show
you how to insert two-wheeler from phonepe
so let's start the video friends at first you
have to open phone pay in your mobile phone
now we have to scroll down to Insurance section
and then we have to click on bike option
say this is the answer section click on bike
now we have to enter our bike registration number
and after that you have to click submit button
if your bike insurance has expired more than
90 days before then click yes otherwise
select no and then click on view quotes
you will see an option here quotes are
loading once all the codes are loaded
it will be sorted out see it is sorted remember
this prices are without personal accident cover
now we have to enable a personal
accident cover see the prices are
varies now now we have to select
the desired Insurance Company
now you will see the owner details
that is name mobile number email ID
Etc now here you have to enter your pan number and
date of birth and after that click continue button
now here you have to enter the nominee details
that is relation with the nominee
nominee name and the nominee Edge
after entering nominal
details click continue button
now check all the fields that you have entered
otherwise click on edit button and then correct
the value and then finally click on buy Plan
now we have to click on pay button
now enter UPI pin and click ok
processing your payment
you have successfully purchased the insurance you
can either click on view details or view policy
you will see the message like this policy
issued successfully congratulations your two
wheeler policy issued you will receive
the certificates in your inbox shortly
to see the policy details just tap on view policy
you can easily download the policy documents
substring by clicking on the download button
so thanks for watching this video
also don't forget to subscribe to
our YouTube channel thank you thank you very much